{
  "Tests": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "1 plus 1 equals to..",
      "Choices": [1, 2, 3],
      "Answer": "2"
    },

    {
      "id": "2",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "2 plus 2 equals to..",
      "Choices": [4, 2, 3],
      "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "3 plus 3 equals to..",
      "Choices": [1, 6, 3],
      "Answer": "6"
    },

    {
      "id": "4",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "6 plus 6 equals to..",
      "Choices": [13, 12, 33],
      "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "1 minus 1 equals to..",
      "Choices": [11, 12, 0],
      "Answer": "0"
    },

    {
      "id": "6",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "2 plus 1 equals to..",
      "Choices": [11, 12, 03],
      "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "1 plus 9 equals to..",
      "Choices": [10, 12, 0],
      "Answer": "10"
    },

    {
      "id": "8",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "11 plus 1 equals to..",
      "Choices": [11, 12, 0],
      "Answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "1 plus 21 equals to..",
      "Choices": [11, 22, 0],
      "Answer": "22"
    },

    {
      "id": "10",
      "Category": "Math",
      "Question": "15 plus 1 equals to..",
      "Choices": [11, 16, 0],
      "Answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "id": "1",
      "Category": "Chemistry",
      "Question": "15 plus 1 equals to..",
      "Choices": [11, 16, 0],
      "Answer": "16"
    }
  ]
}
